https://add.org/terms-conditions/

Join ADDA
What’s ADHD?
JOIN ADDA
Search for:
Join ADDA
What’s ADHD?
JOIN ADDA
Search for:
TERMS & CONDITIONS
Home TERMS & CONDITIONS
You are ADDA. When you use services from or through ADDA or buy products through ADDA, you’re helping yourself. We work with professionals and companies serving adults with ADHD because we want to encourage them to continue creating products and services for us!
PRIVACY POLICY
How will we use information about you?
ADDA will use any collected information to process your order, manage your account, send you newsletters and offers of other products, services or programs.
We will never share your information with any 3rd party without express permission from you.
If at any time you would like to cancel your account, or cease receiving communications from ADDA, simply contact us via this contact form.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, accounting, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
ADDA’s Online Shop
Important: Appearing in ADDA’s Catalog is Not Necessarily an Endorsement
There are great products and services available for adults with ADHD, and when companies list their offer in the ADDA catalog, you benefit, not only from ADDA’s great services, but by discovering new products and services that may serve you well.
You should assume ADDA has a relationship with the sellers we link to in our emails or our online catalog. They may receive compensation if you buy products or services. Take recommendations with the amount of salt you deem appropriate. When our partners sell through ADDA, all revenue goes to support ADDA’s services. Shopping at ADDA helps us help you.
We’ll never tell you what to buy or say that one product or service is better than another, but we know you want to help ADDA, and we want to keep helping you. ADDA will to continue its mission of helping adults with ADHD live better lives, and we encourage you to join us in this endeavor.
Shop with ADDA, and help other adults with ADHD by providing your feedback. If you’ve benefited from a product or service, let us know by rating the product in the catalog.
As always, thank you for your continued commitment to this wonderful organization!
Our partners provide most products and services in our catalog, and when you make your purchase through their Web site, their policies apply to your purchase. When you purchase ADDA’s own products or services, the following policies apply:
ADDA Merchandise Refund Policy
Refunds for merchandise shall only be issued upon the return, in good order, of the merchandise.  Returns shall be at the purchaser’s expense.  Items must be returned within 30 days of purchase.
ADDA Refund Policy – Other items and Events
There shall be no refunds for purchases/downloads of electronic media. All events/seminars/trainings shall be subject to a refund policy established for that event. Refund policy shall be published via the ADDA website for the event in advance of the event.
